A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Second Administration, Series 37.2 FA439A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Second Administration, 1963-1966; 2; 120 microform reels
  - Government (Reel 35, Reel 36, Reel 37, Reel 38, Reel 39, Reel 40, Reel 41, Reel 42, Reel 43, Reel 44)
    - State (Reel 42, Reel 43)
      - Arizona (Reel 42, Frame 164)
      - Alaska (Reel 42, Frame 165)
      - Arkansas (Reel 42, Frame 167)
      - California (Reel 42, Frame 168)
      - Colorado (Reel 42, Frame 177)
      - Connecticut (Reel 42, Frame 178)
      - Florida (Reel 42, Frame 181)
      - Georgia (Reel 42, Frame 186)
      - Idaho (Reel 42, Frame 188)
      - Illinois (Reel 42, Frame 190)
      - Kentucky (Reel 42, Frame 193)
      - Louisiana (Reel 42, Frame 195)
      - Maryland (Reel 42, Frame 197)
      - Massachusetts (Reel 42, Frame 199)
      - Michigan (Reel 42, Frame 205)
      - Minnesota (Reel 42, Frame 212)
      - New Hampshire (Reel 42, Frame 217)
      - New Jersey (Reel 42, Frame 218)
      - North Carolina (Reel 42, Frame 232)
      - Ohio (Reel 42, Frame 234)
      - Oklahoma (Reel 42, Frame 237)
      - Oregon (Reel 42, Frame 241)
      - Pennsylvania (Reel 42, Frame 243)
      - Rhode Island (Reel 43, Frame 2)
      - Texas (Reel 43, Frame 3)
      - Washington (Reel 43, Frame 5)
      - West Virginia (Reel 43, Frame 6)
      - Wyoming (Reel 43, Frame 8)
      - A-Z (Reel 43, Frame 9)
      - General (Reel 43, Frame 27)
    - Local (Reel 43, Reel 44)
      - Towns and Villages A-Z (Reel 43, Frame 35)
      - Police Training (Reel 43, Frame 197)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 43, Frame 212)
      - General
        - 1963-1966 (Reel 43, Frame 228)
        - 1963-1968 (Reel 44, Frame 5)
      - New Citizens (Reel 44, Frame 15)
  - Health & Sanitation (Reel 44, Reel 45, Reel 46)
    - Department of (Reel 44, Frame 115)
    - Hospitals A-Z (Reel 44, Frame 118)
    - Hospitals & Nursing Homes (Reel 44)
      - General (Reel 44, Frame 220)
    - Topics (Reel 44, Reel 45, Reel 46)
      - Air Pollution
        - 1966 February-December (Reel 44, Frame 225)
        - 1963 February-1966 December (Reel 45, Frame 4)
      - Alcoholism (Reel 45, Frame 38)
      - Birth Control (Reel 45, Frame 58)
      - Cancer (Reel 45, Frame 69)
      - Narcotics (Reel 45, Frame 75)
      - Sewage, 1965-1966 (Reel 45, Frame 229)
      - Sewage, 1963-1964 (Reel 46, Frame 3)
      - Radiation (Reel 46, Frame 5)
      - Water Pollution (Reel 46, Frame 19)
    - Topics (Reel 118)
      - Water Pollution (Reel 118)
        - Governor's Program (Reel 118, Frame 7)
        - General (Reel 118, Frame 67)
        - Water Supply (Reel 118, Frame 76)
    - General (Reel 118, Frame 105)
  - Honorary Designation (Reel 118, Reel 119)
    - 1966 January-December (Reel 118, Frame 211)
    - 1963 January-1966 February (Reel 119, Frame 7)
  - Horse Racing (Reel 48, Reel 119)
    - Horse Racing (Reel 48)
      - Harness Racing Commission (Reel 48, Frame 5)
        - General (Reel 48, Frame 22)
      - General (Reel 48, Frame 29)
    - Horse Racing (Reel 119)
      - Flats (Reel 119)
        - New York State Racing Commission (Reel 119, Frame 139)
        - Canandaigua (Reel 119, Frame 160)
        - Governor's Conference for the Saratoga Thoroughbred Racing Centennial (Reel 119, Frame 168)
      - Harness (Reel 119, Frame 175)
  - Housing (Reel 48, Reel 49)
    - Construction & Repairs (Reel 48)
      - Urban Renewal (Reel 48, Frame 37)
    - Division of (Reel 48, Frame 89)
    - Construction & Repairs (Reel 48)
      - Finances (Reel 48, Frame 121)
      - General (Reel 48, Frame 135)
    - Low and Middle Income (Reel 48, Frame 142)
    - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission (Reel 48, Frame 177)
    - Projects (Reel 48, Frame 187)
    - Rent Control (Reel 48, Reel 49)
      - 1963 July-1966 (Reel 48, Frame 222)
      - 1963 January-July (Reel 49, Frame 2)
    - Tenant Problems Eviction (Reel 49, Frame 12)
    - Tenant Problems General (Reel 49, Frame 15)
    - General (Reel 49, Frame 24)
  - Insurance (Reel 49, Reel 50)
    - Department of (Reel 49, Frame 42)
    - Auto Liability Insurance (Reel 49, Frame 92)
    - Fire Insurance (Reel 49, Frame 121)
    - Health Insurance for the Aged (Reel 49, Reel 50)
      - 1966 May-December (Reel 49, Frame 229)
      - 1963-1966 June (Reel 50, Frame 1)
    - Health Insurance (Reel 50)
      - Rates (Reel 50, Frame 77)
      - Blue Cross & Blue Shield (Reel 50, Frame 133)
      - State Employees (Reel 50, Frame 146)
      - Life Insurance (Reel 50, Frame 150)
      - General (Reel 50, Frame 170)
  - Investigations (Reel 50, Reel 51)
    - Boxing (Reel 50, Frame 174)
    - Liquor (Reel 50, Frame 176)
      - Moreland Commission (Reel 50, Frame 179)
    - General (Reel 50, Reel 51)
      - A - Westchester County, 1964 (Reel 50, Frame 206)
      - Westchester County, 1963 (Reel 51, Frame 7)
      - General (Reel 51, Frame 16)
  - Judiciary (Reel 51, Reel 52)
    - Courts (Reel 51, Reel 52)
      - A-Z (Reel 51, Frame 57)
      - New York City Courts (Reel 51, Frame 79)
      - County Courts A-Z (Reel 51, Frame 109)
      - New York City Courts (Reel 51, Frame 132)
      - Family Court (Reel 51, Frame 170)
      - Fun Fair Park Case (Reel 51, Frame 187)
      - Litigation Cases (Reel 51, Reel 52)
        - 1964 November-1966 (Reel 51, Frame 198)
        - 1963-1964 November (Reel 52, Frame 2)
      - Supreme Court (Reel 52, Frame 61)
      - Surrogates Court (Reel 52, Frame 98)
      - General (Reel 52, Frame 103)
  - Labor (Reel 52, Reel 53, Reel 54, Reel 55, Reel 56, Reel 57)
    - Department of (Reel 52, Frame 230)
    - Labor Relations Act (Reel 52, Frame 239)
    - Labor Relations Act (Reel 53, Frame 3)
    - Labor Relations Board (Reel 53, Frame 57)
    - Department of (Reel 53)
      - Labor Relations (Reel 53, Frame 74)
      - Division of Manpower (Reel 53, Frame 81)
      - Migrant Labor (Reel 53, Frame 118)
      - State Insurance Fund (Reel 53, Frame 127)
      - General (Reel 53, Frame 133)
    - Benefits (Reel 53, Reel 54, Reel 55)
      - Unemployment Insurance
        - 1966 (Reel 53, Frame 189)
        - 1963-1966 January (Reel 54, Frame 7)
      - Workmen's Compensation
        - 1965-1966 (Reel 54, Frame 208)
        - 1964-1966 (Reel 55, Frame 4)
    - Mediation & Arbitration (Reel 55)
      - Commission of Public Concern (Reel 55, Frame 51)
      - State Board of Mediation (Reel 55, Frame 60)
    - Minimum Wage (Reel 55, Frame 77)
    - Social Security (Reel 55, Frame 160)
    - Strikes (Reel 55, Reel 56)
      - Dock Strikes (Reel 55, Frame 189)
      - Newspaper Strike (Reel 55, Frame 192)
      - Teacher Stikes
        - 1966 March-May (Reel 55, Frame 236)
        - 1963 July-1966 January (Reel 56, Frame 7)
      - Transit Strike (Reel 56, Frame 12)
      - General (Reel 56, Frame 87)
    - Unemployment (Reel 56, Reel 57)
      - Employment, Division of (Reel 56, Frame 142)
        - Employment Services (Reel 56, Frame 144)
          - Unemployment Insurance (Reel 56, Frame 157)
          - General (Reel 56, Frame 211)
      - General (Reel 57, Frame 6)
    - Workmen's Compensation Board (Reel 57)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 57, Frame 14)
      - General (Reel 57, Frame 15)
    - Workmen's Compensation Review Committee (Reel 57, Frame 29)
    - General (Reel 57, Frame 56)
  - Law (Reel 57, Reel 58, Reel 59)
    - Department of (Reel 57)
      - Complaints & Proceedings (Reel 57)
        - Notice of Proceedings (Reel 57, Frame 115)
        - General (Reel 57, Frame 131)
      - Consumer Fraud Bureau (Reel 57, Frame 134)
      - Civil Rights Bureau (Reel 57, Frame 141)
      - General (Reel 57, Frame 158)
    - General (Reel 57, Reel 58, Reel 59)
      - ABC Law (Reel 57, Frame 167)
      - Constitutional Convention (Reel 57, Frame 188)
      - Daylight Savings Time (Reel 57, Frame 197)
      - Domestic Relations (Reel 57, Frame 203)
      - Election Law
        - Reapportionment
          - 1965 July-1966 (Reel 57, Frame 258)
          - 1963-1966 August (Reel 58, Frame 6)
        - Qualification (Reel 58, Frame 115)
        - General (Reel 58, Frame 175)
      - Holidays (Reel 58, Frame 231)
      - Obscene Literature
        - 1964 September-1966 (Reel 58, Frame 234)
        - 1963-1964 August (Reel 59, Frame 7)
      - School Prayer (Reel 59, Frame 28)
      - Sabbath Law (Reel 59, Frame 41)
      - Sullivan Law (Reel 59, Frame 53)
      - General (Reel 59, Frame 57)
  - Legislation
    - 1963 (Reel 18, Reel 19, Reel 20)
      - Aging (Reel 18, Frame 180)
      - Agriculture & Markets (Reel 18, Frame 181)
      - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 18, Frame 198)
      - Banking (Reel 18, Frame 199)
      - Civil Defense (Reel 18, Frame 203)
      - Commerce (Reel 18, Frame 204)
      - Conservation (Reel 18, Frame 205)
      - Correction (Reel 18, Frame 211)
      - Discrimination (Reel 18, Frame 212)
      - Education (Reel 18, Frame 217)
      - Fiscal (Reel 18, Frame 235)
      - Education (Reel 19, Frame 5)
      - Government (Reel 19, Frame 30)
      - Housing (Reel 19, Frame 52)
      - Insurance (Reel 19, Frame 57)
      - Labor (Reel 19, Frame 69)
      - Judicial (Reel 19, Frame 92)
      - Labor (Reel 19, Frame 98)
      - Law (Reel 19, Frame 127)
      - Licensing (Reel 19, Frame 174)
      - Mental Hygiene (Reel 19, Frame 215)
      - Military & Naval (Reel 19, Frame 216)
      - Parks & Recreational Facilities (Reel 19, Frame 216)
      - Personnel Administration (Reel 19, Frame 224)
      - Personnel Administration (Reel 20, Frame 5)
      - Property (Reel 20, Frame 14)
      - Public Safety (Reel 20, Frame 18)
      - Public Utilities (Reel 20, Frame 27)
      - Public Works (Reel 20, Frame 33)
      - Social Welfare (Reel 20, Frame 38)
      - General (Reel 20, Frame 45)
    - 1966 (Reel 59, Reel 60, Reel 61, Reel 62, Reel 63, Reel 64)
      - Federal (Reel 59, Frame 115)
      - Aging (Reel 59, Frame 193)
      - Agriculture (Reel 59, Frame 199)
      - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 59, Frame 212)
      - Banking (Reel 59, Frame 242)
      - Commerce (Reel 60, Frame 5)
      - Conservation (Reel 60, Frame 18)
      - Correction (Reel 60, Frame 45)
      - Discrimination (Reel 60, Frame 55)
      - Education (Reel 60, Frame 56)
      - Fiscal (Reel 61, Frame 19)
      - Government (Reel 61, Frame 132)
      - Health (Reel 61, Frame 145)
      - Horse Racing (Reel 61, Frame 221)
      - Housing (Reel 61, Frame 224)
      - Insurance
        - 1966 March-September (Reel 61, Frame 250)
        - 1966 January-March (Reel 62, Frame 2)
      - Judiciary (Reel 62, Frame 5)
      - Labor (Reel 62, Frame 37)
      - Law (Reel 62, Frame 149)
      - Licensing (Reel 62, Frame 232)
      - Mental Hygiene
        - 1966 May-October (Reel 62, Frame 240)
        - 1966 January-March (Reel 63, Frame 4)
      - Military & Naval (Reel 63, Frame 7)
      - Parks & Recreational Facilities (Reel 63, Frame 8)
      - Personnel Administration (Reel 63, Frame 9)
      - Property
        - 1966 March-August (Reel 63, Frame 234)
        - 1966 February-March (Reel 64, Frame 5)
      - Public Safety (Reel 64, Frame 6)
      - Public Utilities (Reel 64, Frame 76)
      - Public Works (Reel 64, Frame 81)
      - Veterans (Reel 64, Frame 102)
      - Welfare (Reel 64, Frame 103)
      - Youth (Reel 64, Frame 134)
      - General (Reel 64, Frame 137)
    - 1965 (Reel 64, Reel 65, Reel 66, Reel 67, Reel 68, Reel 69, Reel 70, Reel 71)
      - Federal (Reel 64, Frame 179)
      - Aging
        - 1965 June-December (Reel 64, Frame 244)
        - 1965 January-June (Reel 65, Frame 5)
      - Agriculture (Reel 65, Frame 7)
      - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 65, Frame 20)
      - Banking (Reel 65, Frame 39)
      - Budget (Reel 65, Frame 64)
      - Commerce (Reel 65, Frame 64)
      - Conservation (Reel 65, Frame 72)
      - Correction (Reel 65, Frame 84)
      - Discrimination (Reel 65, Frame 91)
      - Education
        - 1965 April-December (Reel 65, Frame 104)
        - 1965 January-June (Reel 66, Frame 4)
      - Executive Clemency (Reel 67, Frame 5)
      - Fiscal (Reel 67, Frame 67)
      - Government (Reel 67, Frame 159)
      - Health & Sanitation
        - 1965 April-December (Reel 67, Frame 189)
        - 1965 January-April (Reel 68, Frame 5)
      - Horse Racing (Reel 68, Frame 17)
      - Housing (Reel 68, Frame 23)
      - Insurance (Reel 68, Frame 74)
      - Judiciary (Reel 68, Frame 100)
      - Labor
        - 1965 April-December (Reel 68, Frame 149)
        - 1965 April-June (Reel 69, Frame 4)
      - Law (Reel 69, Frame 105)
      - Licensing
        - 1965 May-December (Reel 69, Frame 228)
        - 1965 January-May (Reel 70, Frame 2)
      - Liquor (Reel 70, Frame 9)
      - Mental Hygiene (Reel 70, Frame 10)
      - Parks & Recreational Facilities (Reel 70, Frame 40)
      - Personnel Administration (Reel 70)
        - Teachers (Reel 70, Frame 58)
        - General (Reel 70, Frame 67)
      - Public Utilities (Reel 70, Frame 187)
      - Public Safety
        - 1965 May-December (Reel 70, Frame 222)
        - 1965 January-May (Reel 71, Frame 9)
      - Property (Reel 71, Frame 17)
      - Public Works (Reel 71, Frame 27)
      - Veterans (Reel 71, Frame 86)
      - Welfare (Reel 71, Frame 89)
      - Youth (Reel 71, Frame 113)
      - General (Reel 71, Frame 123)
    - 1964 (Reel 71, Reel 72, Reel 73, Reel 74)
      - Federal (Reel 71, Frame 211)
      - Agriculture & Markets
        - 1964 February-June (Reel 71, Frame 229)
        - 1964 January-February (Reel 72, Frame 6)
      - Administration (Reel 72, Frame 9)
      - Authorities & Commission (Reel 72, Frame 10)
      - Civil Defense (Reel 72, Frame 21)
      - Commerce (Reel 72, Frame 22)
      - Conservation (Reel 72, Frame 31)
      - Correction (Reel 72, Frame 43)
      - Discrimination (Reel 72, Frame 45)
      - Education (Reel 72, Frame 54)
      - Fiscal (Reel 72, Frame 226)
      - Fiscal (Reel 73, Frame 12)
      - Government (Reel 73, Frame 25)
      - Fund Raising Campaign (Reel 73, Frame 38)
      - Housing (Reel 73, Frame 44)
      - Insurance (Reel 73, Frame 68)
      - Health & Sanitation (Reel 73, Frame 94)
      - Horse Racing (Reel 73, Frame 112)
      - Health & Sanitation (Reel 73, Frame 113)
      - Law
        - 1964 March-December (Reel 73, Frame 185)
        - 1964 January-March (Reel 74, Frame 5)
      - Licensing (Reel 74, Frame 52)
      - Mental Hygiene (Reel 74, Frame 88)
      - Personnel Administration (Reel 74, Frame 98)
    - 1964 (Reel 113, Reel 117)
      - State
        - Personnel Administration (Reel 113, Frame 5)
        - Property (Reel 113, Frame 87)
        - Public Safety (Reel 113, Frame 96)
        - Judiciary (Reel 113, Frame 114)
        - Labor (Reel 113, Frame 142)
        - Welfare (Reel 113, Frame 208)
        - Youth (Reel 113, Frame 231)
        - Public Safety (Reel 117)
          - 1964 January-March (Reel 117, Frame 7)
        - Public Utilities (Reel 117, Frame 24)
        - Public Works (Reel 117, Frame 36)
        - Personnel Administration (Reel 117, Frame 66)
        - General (Reel 117, Frame 82)
      - Federal (Reel 117, Frame 128)
    - General, undated (Reel 74)
      - Federal (Reel 74)
        - Committee of (Reel 74, Frame 115)
        - General (Reel 74, Frame 120)
  - Legislature (Reel 74, Reel 75)
    - Committee of (Reel 74, Frame 143)
    - Messages (Reel 74, Frame 195)
    - State (Reel 74, Frame 236)
      - Special Session (Reel 74, Frame 237)
      - Special Session (Reel 75, Frame 10)
    - General (Reel 75, Frame 33)
  - Licensing (Reel 75)
    - Chiropractor (Reel 75, Frame 64)
    - Liquor (Reel 75, Frame 103)
    - General (Reel 75, Frame 195)
  - Mental Hygiene (Reel 76, Reel 77)
    - Department of (Reel 76, Frame 1)
    - Institutions (Reel 76)
      - Manhattan State Hospital (Reel 76, Frame 45)
      - Psychiatric Institute (Reel 76, Frame 55)
      - Rockland State Hospital (Reel 76, Frame 59)
      - Rome State School (Reel 76, Frame 68)
      - Suffolk State School (Reel 76, Frame 80)
      - Willowbrook State School (Reel 76, Frame 87)
      - A-Z (Reel 76, Frame 101)
      - General (Reel 76, Frame 161)
    - General (Reel 76, Reel 77)
      - Mental Health Program (Reel 76, Frame 190)
      - Mental Retardation (Reel 76, Frame 209)
      - Regional Planning Committees on Mental Disorders (Reel 76, Frame 230)
      - Regional Planning Committees on Mental Disorders (Reel 77, Frame 5)
      - Narcotics Addiction Control Commmission (Reel 77, Frame 8)
      - General (Reel 77, Frame 19)
  - Military & Naval (Reel 77, Reel 78)
    - State National Guard Armories (Reel 77, Frame 67)
    - Air National Guard (Reel 77, Frame 92)
    - National Guard (Reel 77, Frame 104)
    - Naval Militia (Reel 77, Frame 148)
    - Military & Naval Affairs, Division of (Reel 77, Frame 150)
    - Military & Naval Reservations (Reel 77, Frame 182)
    - Military & Naval Reservations (Reel 78, Frame 5)
    - General (Reel 78)
      - Selective Service (Reel 78, Frame 12)
      - Conspicuous Service Cross (Reel 78, Frame 18)
      - State Flags (Reel 78, Frame 23)
    - Federal (Reel 78)
      - U.S. Air Force (Reel 78, Frame 32)
      - U.S. Army (Reel 78, Frame 35)
      - Naval Air Reserve (Reel 78, Frame 53)
      - U.S. Coast Guard (Reel 78, Frame 57)
  - Parks & Recreation Facilities (Reel 78)
    - Parks (Reel 78, Frame 62)
    - Winter Sports (Reel 78, Frame 161)
    - General (Reel 78, Frame 182)
  - Personnel Administration (Reel 78, Reel 79, Reel 81, Reel 82)
    - Civil Service Department (Reel 78, Frame 208)
    - Civil Service Department (Reel 79, Frame 5)
    - State Employees (Reel 79, Reel 81)
      - Attendance Rule
        - 1963 March-1966 December (Reel 79, Frame 211)
        - 1963 (Reel 81, Frame 7)
      - Code of Ethics (Reel 81, Frame 23)
    - Civil Service (Reel 81, Reel 82)
      - Employees Grievances (Reel 81)
        - Appointments (Reel 81, Frame 24)
        - Board of Decisions (Reel 81, Frame 35)
        - Payroll Problems (Reel 81, Frame 36)
        - Reinstatements (Reel 81, Frame 38)
        - Termination (Reel 81, Frame 41)
        - General (Reel 81, Frame 60)
      - Attendance Rules (Reel 81, Frame 94)
      - State Employees
        - Parking (Reel 81, Frame 104)
        - Retirement (Reel 81, Frame 105)
        - Salaries (Reel 81, Frame 143)
        - General
          - 1966 July-December (Reel 81, Frame 233)
          - 1963 January-1966 July (Reel 82, Frame 2)
      - Local (Reel 82)
        - New York City Police (Reel 82, Frame 66)
        - City of New York (Reel 82, Frame 68)
        - Government County (Reel 82, Frame 81)
        - Government Towns & Villages (Reel 82, Frame 84)
        - General (Reel 82, Frame 85)
      - Teachers (Reel 82)
        - Retirement (Reel 82, Frame 94)
        - General (Reel 82, Frame 139)
      - General (Reel 82, Frame 181)
  - Politics (Reel 82, Reel 83)
    - General
      - 1966 November-1967 February (Reel 82, Frame 189)
      - 1963 March-1966 November (Reel 83, Frame 1)
  - Property (Reel 83, Reel 84)
    - Federal (Reel 83)
      - Surplus Property (Reel 83, Frame 128)
    - Acquisitions & Purchases (Reel 83, Reel 84)
      - Highways (Reel 83, Frame 185)
      - State University (Reel 83)
        - 1964 October-1966 September (Reel 83, Frame 231)
      - State University (Reel 84, Frame 4)
      - Wartbury Orphan Farm School (Reel 84, Frame 9)
      - General (Reel 84, Frame 16)
      - Parks (Reel 84, Frame 48)
      - General (Reel 84, Frame 58)
      - State (Reel 84)
        - General (Reel 84, Frame 110)
  - Public Safety (Reel 84, Reel 85, Reel 86, Reel 87)
    - Federal (Reel 84, Frame 118)
    - Highway Safety (Reel 84, Reel 85)
      - New York Citizens Council on Traffic Safety (Reel 84, Frame 120)
      - Drunk Drivers (Reel 84, Frame 211)
      - Holiday Weekends (Reel 84, Frame 214)
      - Seat Belts (Reel 84, Frame 222)
      - Speed Limits (Reel 84, Frame 224)
      - Specific Routes
        - 224 & 14 (Reel 84, Frame 240)
        - 224 & 14 (Reel 85, Frame 8)
        - 25A (Reel 85, Frame 14)
        - 81 (Reel 85, Frame 27)
      - Traffic Signals (Reel 85, Frame 39)
      - Safe Car Program (Reel 85, Frame 72)
      - General (Reel 85, Frame 100)
    - State (Reel 85, Reel 86)
      - Governor's Conference on Crime
        - 1966 January-May (Reel 85, Frame 243)
        - 1966 March-June (Reel 86, Frame 4)
      - Crime (Reel 86)
        - General (Reel 86, Frame 15)
    - Firearms (Reel 86, Frame 94)
    - State Police (Reel 86, Reel 87)
      - Troopers Complaints (Reel 86, Frame 146)
      - Division of (Reel 86, Frame 155)
      - Substation (Reel 86, Frame 157)
      - Division of (Reel 86)
        - Troopers (Reel 86)
          - Appointments (Reel 86, Frame 168)
          - Letters of Commendation (Reel 86, Frame 171)
          - Reinstatements (Reel 86, Frame 186)
          - General (Reel 86, Frame 189)
      - Division of
        - General
          - 1966 January-December (Reel 86, Frame 224)
          - 1963 January-1966 January (Reel 87, Frame 5)
    - State (Reel 87)
      - General (Reel 87)
        - Local Police Reports (Reel 87, Frame 24)
        - General (Reel 87, Frame 41)
  - Public Utilities (Reel 87, Reel 88, Reel 89, Reel 90, Reel 91)
    - Communication (Reel 87, Frame 76)
    - Fuel (Reel 87)
      - Gas (Reel 87, Frame 85)
      - Petroleum Products (Reel 87, Frame 91)
    - Power (Reel 87, Reel 88, Reel 89)
      - Atomic
        - Nuclear Tests (Reel 87, Frame 106)
          - 1963 May-1966 (Reel 87, Frame 134)
          - 1963 January-May (Reel 88, Frame 7)
      - Industrial
        - 1964 April-1966 (Reel 88, Frame 13)
        - 1963 April-1964 March (Reel 89, Frame 4)
      - General (Reel 89, Frame 61)
    - Transportation
      - Railroad (Reel 89, Reel 90)
        - Full Crew Law (Reel 89, Frame 129)
        - Long Island Railroad (Reel 89, Frame 177)
        - New Haven Railroad
          - 1965 June-1966 September (Reel 89, Frame 231)
          - 1965 January-June (Reel 90, Frame 2)
        - New York Central Railroad (Reel 90, Frame 92)
        - New Haven Railroad, 1963-1964 (Reel 90, Frame 104)
        - General (Reel 90, Frame 139)
      - Northeast Airlines (Reel 90, Frame 189)
      - Office of (Reel 90, Frame 190)
      - General (Reel 90, Reel 91)
        - 1966 (Reel 90, Frame 196)
        - 1963-1966 August (Reel 91, Frame 5)
    - General (Reel 91, Frame 85)
  - Public Works (Reel 91, Reel 92, Reel 93, Reel 94)
    - Buildings (Reel 91, Frame 113)
      - Capital (Reel 91, Frame 116)
      - Harlem (Reel 91, Frame 131)
      - General (Reel 91, Frame 139)
    - Canals & Waterways (Reel 91, Reel 92)
      - Barge Canal (Reel 91, Frame 159)
      - Lake Champlain Seaway (Reel 91, Frame 172)
      - Erie Canal (Reel 91, Frame 179)
      - Little Neck Bay (Reel 91, Frame 181)
      - General
        - 1965-1966 (Reel 91, Frame 204)
        - 1963 February-1965 February (Reel 92, Frame 5)
    - Department of (Reel 92)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 92, Frame 44)
      - General (Reel 92, Frame 56)
    - Highways (Reel 92, Reel 93, Reel 94)
      - Atlantic Expressway (Reel 92, Frame 123)
      - Aurora Expressway (Reel 92, Frame 127)
      - Alexandria - Morristown Scenic Highway (Reel 92, Frame 131)
      - Highway Appropriations (Reel 92, Frame 132)
      - Highway Construction (Reel 92, Frame 135)
      - Cross-Brooklyn Expressway (Reel 92, Frame 146)
      - Cross-County Parkway (Reel 92, Frame 151)
      - Drake's Drawbridge (Reel 92, Frame 162)
      - Route 84 (Reel 92, Frame 167)
      - Route 81 (Reel 92, Frame 172)
      - Route 54A (Reel 92, Frame 241)
      - Fire Island (Reel 93, Frame 1, 24)
      - Route 55 (Reel 93, Frame 4, 27)
      - Hudson River Expressway (Reel 93, Frame 6, 29)
      - Lower Hudson Valley Expressway (Reel 93, Frame 35)